Hi. my name is Peter Parker.
You don't remember me. but I have something
to tell you that's going to sound crazy.
But it's the truth.
And I know you're going to believe me because
you're very good at telling when I'm lying.
E.V.. can you check the calibration of my
targeting matrix? That doesn't feel zero to me.
Checking the target calibration.
Hey. E.V.. take five.
Standing five.
We used to know each other.
We were together.
But something bad was going to happen.
And the only way to stop it
was to make everyone forget me.
First day in my team is go! Oh
my gosh. we're here! We made it!
MJ. come on.
Including you.
Pretend like you're not the happiest you've
ever been in your entire life right now.
I can't believe it!
Because I'm not just Peter Parker.
I'm Spider-Man.
And sometimes. Spider-Man has to do the hard
thing even if it breaks Peter Parker's heart.
And maybe that's my responsibility
to live alone with the truth.
But the truth is. MJ. that I love you.
And I hope to deep down something inside
of you remembers that you love me too.
Suspect is five. eight.
five. ten. Medium build.
But until then. I'm just
going to be Spider-Man.
Members of the Man Fresh Five. let me give
you a happy. entertained Spider-Man yesterday.
Hey!
You live on the same floor.
What?
Cool.
Does anybody ever come up here?
Not unless they like asbestos.
We've just been using it for storage.
That's perfect.
Hey everyone. Sophomore Year Ned is back.
Only the wise one.
Flyer.
Let's go!
Whoa!
What?
What is on your face?
How do you feel about it?
I mean. you look like an assistant coach.
Whoa!
You sure you want to do this. Scorpion?
Did you miss me. Spidey?
If I drop you from here. how long
will you take to get to the ground?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Let's end this on a high note. huh?
Yo. Lonnie.
What happened?
DeWolff!
All the evidence you're gonna
need is in the trunk of his car.
You trying to take my job. Spider Man?
Hey. you guys are the professionals.
I'm just a volunteer.
It's a new New York.
Thanks to Spider Man crime
rate have droped to a record low.
Police and damage control give
much of the credit to the masked hero.
Initiate HUD test.
Armed robbery is underway at Union Bank.
In the past six months. he has
taken down every major crime lord
across the divided burrows. including
the superpowered ninja group "The Hand".
He is the pride of New York City.
He hero every grown-up relies on him.
And every kid wants to be.
Final semester. MIT.
Oh my gosh. we're graduating in a month.
We made so many memories.
Where do I begin?
Night swimming in the Charles
River with Jim and Wiley.
The infamous food fighter
in the Banana Lounge.
Pulling all nighters Stud
5 with MJ and Nate Dawg.
It feels like yesterday I
was sitting on a roof with MJ..
Dreaming about coming here
together. I still can't believe we did it.
I'm so grateful for all
the friends that I've made.
I couldn't imagine going
thru this with anyone else.
Ned. what do you think
is actually watching these?
I don't know. but maybe someone.
- Okay. bye someone! What? No!
- Bye. We're done. Yeah. we're done.
I mean. we're talking about
downtown Brooklyn in broad daylight.
A high profile job like that.
you know the fossil is involved.
Yeah. I hear you. but can you prove it?
Yeah. I'm going through
his financial records.
and I'm following his crew every night.
Do you do anything besides work?
You know the saying:
"You do something you love..
You don't work a day in your life."
Gimme a...
Mom. where's my calculator?
Trust me.
Being married to the job never ends well.
Don't worry about it. I'll be okay.
Oh. yeah?
You're still getting them
headaches. though?
Yeah. but I'll be fine.
I don't know. man. I think your
body's trying to tell you something.
Like. you need to get out of
that suit every once in a while.
Mom. do you know where my calculator is?
I don't know. Papi.
What you need is some
real human connection.
Oh. what? We're not connecting?
I don't know your name. your
face. or nothing about you.
I don't think you've ever asked
me a question about my life.
Sure I have.
Yeah. what are my kids' names?
Well. for starters. your son's name's Papi.
Is it Spider-Man?
I can't tell you that. sweetheart.
That means it's Spider-Man.
Oh. gosh.
A hijack's tank is heading
southbound past 34th Street.
All available units respond.
Hey. you getting this?
More work? Lucky you!
Okay. I'll see you out there.
I'm so sorry. I got to go.
Holy moly!
I got you. Spidey!
I don't need you!
Hey. what's up?
You okay?
Yeah. you okay?
See you later!
I wouldn't know it just by looking at it. but this very
street was completely destroyed in the Battle of New York.
Oh!
Come on. come on. come on!
Oh God!
The hell. Frank!
You just hit me with the van!
Quit your whimpering.
We're not doing that again. Frank.
You're goddamn right. we're not.
This time you're gonna
get the hell out of my way.
You mean. instead of saving your life?
You're going to talk about
that Staten Island bullshit again?
Oh. well. you said it not me.
Look. man. you can't just shoot
yourself out of every situation.
Innocent people get hurt.
What do you think's down-range
to that tank. dum dum?
Suit yourself.
Jackass.
This friggin' guy.
Go home. Frank!
I'm gonna kill this kid.
DeWolff.
You're gonna stop that thing or what?
It's heading straight for the
Damage Control detention center.
I'm trying.
Try harder.
There's another scary
dude locked up in there.
Who do you think put them in there?
Let's go. Scorpion.
Moving day.
All right. everybody. clear out!
This guy's armed and dangerous.
Uh. get out of the vehicle. ma'am.
I was thinking the same thing.
Spider-man?
Where am I?
Move! Move! Move!
- Keep her for questioning.
- Clear the building.
Enjoy the ride. Scorpion.
What are we seeing much
daylight? It's Supermax.
Scorpions are nocturnal. buddy.
The building is under attack.
Get the prisoner out of here now.
The building is in breach.
Go.
You gotta take off now.
The building is in breach.
Go. Go.
Change of plans!
Take it to the Alabama Bellevue.
What?
That's an order from Director Metzger.
Go. Now.
Copy that.
Hey! What?
How did I get up here?
Spider-Man!
Save me. would you?
Who are you?
You can see me.
Tell me who you are.
You first.
Hey.
You pushed me out.
Interesting.
What the hell was that?
Did you just try to jump into my mind?
No.
The whole time you've been chasing me..
You forgot to ask yourself
a very important position.
What's in the tank?
What?
Spider-Man?
What just happened?
I don't know.
Okay. good job.
You guys okay?
Are you good?
I swear.
All the things they said I did..
I don't remember doing any of them.
It's okay. it's okay.
Look. let these people
take good care of you.
I would never hurt you.
Okay.
I love you. Spider-Man.
Yeah. all right. buddy. all right.
Hey. what do you got?
Here. get this.
Chopper took Scorpion to Bellevue.
Ten minutes later. the guard
walked him right on the door.
What?
Mm-hmm.
What about the tank?
Stolen from the Damage Control warehouse in
Brooklyn The driver was a janitor who worked there.
You got a motive?
Nada.
And no criminal record.
Scorpion must have gotten to her somehow.
Yeah. maybe.
What do you mean. maybe?
I'm mean...
I don't know.
But I know someone that might be.
Where you going?
You keep following the leads on Scorpion.
I'm going to go talk to someone.
Hi.
Is this 350 Brighton Beach?
[ Speaking foreign language ]
Okay.
And I think I know what that means.
Take off your clothes.
Uh. what?
You don't want clothes in the banya.
Ditch the leotard.
This is not a leotard.
Your text said that this was your office.
This is my office.
Get in.
I'm fine. thanks. I'll just..
My office. my rules.
This way. you get to
enjoy a nice relaxing soak.
And I get to see that you
don't have any weapons.
And we both win.
Okay.
Yeah.
Really?
Would you never take that off?
No. you know. it fits the
whole anonymous thing.
Even for your girlfriend
or boyfriend or whatever?
There's a lot of conjecture online.
And super graphic artwork.
The one with you and the ten Mysterios..
Yea yea yea. I've seen it.
It's a bit hard to unsee to be honest..
I just want to keep to myself.
All by yourself all the time?
No wonder you're so sad.
I'm not so sad.
Could we just talk about what I came here to
talk to you about the attack on Damage Control?
Yes.
So that is more.. "Your" area.
Like small potato stuff.
Whereas the new Avengers
are focusing on big potato stuff.
Right. okay.
Well. there's more to it than that.
You know. deal with the driver
and the others who were helping.
It was like someone was
talking to me through them.
Like someone was looking
at me through their eyes.
And you're wondering if it's mind control.
Exactly.
Like how they used on me in the red room.
And the other widows.
Right.
No. I don't think so.
I actually think it's probably
more like "possession".
Possession?
Mm-hmm.
Like a ghost or a demon or
in Russia we have "leshy".
Leshy rules the forest and can possess...
Sorry.
Whatever it is. they're
looking for something.
This is the fourth attack on the
damage control facility this month.
What do you think they're looking for?
I don't know.
But you know what?
After the attack today.
there was a cross-agency cyber
security alert that got triggered.
Someone accessed the
Damage Control restricted servers.
Using credentials from 13
employees from the way station.
They all searched for the same thing.
VMAX.
VMAX?
What does that mean?
I mean. it could be alien tip or secretive
weapon programs or launch codes or...
I don't know.
This is for you to figure out.
This is a small baby potato stuff.
Not big potato brain stuff - Okay
okay. you don't to shout about it. Jeez.
Maybe I'll just go ask
Damage Control myself.
You know. you're not
completely anonymous anymore.
I've seen your belly button.
Okay.
Bye...
Hi. I got an appointment with...
Director Metzger.
Yes.
Please step through the scanner.
Enhanced human detected.
Superior strength.
Superior agility.
Heightened senses.
Exogenous DNA: Arachnid.
Please remove your face
covering for identity scan.
Oh no. I can't do that.
that's not possible.
Failure to remove your face covering
will result in defensive measures.
Defensive measures?
What do you want?
Whoa. whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. guys. guys. guys.
I can't take my mask off.
I'm sorry.
Spider-Man.
He's all right.
At ease.
My apologies.
We are so glad you're here.
Bill Metzger.
Director of Damage Control.
How are you?
I'm good. thank you.
We have to beef up security around here.
but I hope we didn't give you a fright.
No. not at all.
All right. come on in this way.
Thanks.
This floor is mostly
research administrative.
Downstairs. we have
incident clean-out. laboratories.
Agent training.
Oh.
Hey. what are they doing here?
It's okay.
The Hand works for us now.
After you brought them in. I
realized that fundamentally.
they're a group of kids without a leader.
All they needed was a little direction.
And suddenly. all the things
that made them dangerous
turned them into an invaluable
part of our security team.
[ Speaking Japanese ]
You can look at the many threats
that face us and see only danger.
Or you can see our opportunity.
Okay.
Wow. look at that.
In the hands of Shocker.
these are a nuisance.
But it doesn't mean we can't
learn from the technology
or respect the innovation.
Our mission is to
redirect destructive energy
into something useful.
That's the true meaning of Damage Control.
I'm sorry.
Be careful with that.
Back this way.
I. uh. wanted to talk to you about
the recent attacks on the agency.
There's been four. right?
Please have a seat.
You are right.
It appears we're faced with
the threat we can't control.
One we can't even see.
But you can.
I saw the security footage.
I also read Detective DeWolff's report.
I believe you understand
exactly what we're up against.
Someone knows something
that can hop into people's minds.
But not yours.
No.
I mean. it tried. but it couldn't.
I'm going to be honest with you.
We're on our heels right now.
God forbid if we were to get
in here and find whatever it is
is looking for the consequences
could be unimaginable.
Well. let me guess.
Is whatever it's looking
for in that giant vault?
There are some things.
because of the nature of my job..
I cannot tell you.
But I believe you are our
best defense against this.
You're the only one who can sense it.
You're the only one who's immune to it.
I'm counting on you to defeat it.
That's pretty good speech. director.
I'll do everything that I can. I promise.
Well. then consider yourself
a friend of Damage Control.
Thank you.
I'll be in touch.
Oh. I wanted to ask.
The phrase Vmax doesn't
mean anything to you.
Does it?
No.
Where'd you hear that?
Oh. it's just. you know.
Nature of being a superhero.
there are some things
I just can't tell you.
Anyway. I'll see you later.
You guys are doing great.
Keep it up.
I don't think Metzger
knows anymore than we do.
but I told him I'd do
whatever I can to help.
You want to help?
The best thing you
could do is find Scorpion.
He's our only lead.
Yeah.
I know.
I have every camera in the city
running a facial recognition scan for him.
That sounds super illegal. Spider-Man.
I'm gonna pretend I didn't hear that.
Yeah. probably for the best.
But look. if he shows his face. we'll know.
Do you have any mini-kegs?
Down that end.
Thanks.
I'll call you back.
Uh-huh.
Easy.
Hey. uh. also. are you gonna
need Shark Fire Energy?
Yeah.
Oh. no. no.
I don't want any.
That stuff will kill you.
You know. all my friends
were drinking them.
and we're in finals. and
now they're addicted.
And so. I'm gonna need
you to not sell me any.
Memorise my face.
Please. do not sell
this guy any sharp fire.
Sure. whatever.
Actually. I'll take one.
The last one.
Maybe two?
And then never sell me any.
Damn it.
Oh.
I see. you've stumbled across my board.
I'm not one of those weirdos.
I swear.
He actually saved me in my
friend's lives two times in high school.
Oh. cool.
Yeah. yeah.
And ever since I've just been
trying to figure out who he is.
not not to unmask him
to the world or anything.
just to know. you know.
and to hopefully thank him face to face.
I actually created this app.
The monitors his sightings.
Wait. you created Spidey Tracker.
You heard of it. Nice.
Where is Spider-Man?
We'll be chatting room right there.
Now. we know he's definitely from Queens.
Not the biggest revelation.
But I have been able to narrow
it down into prime suspects.
Yeah.
If you know where they were.
it would really blow your mind.
I'm sure.
Ned. by the way.
Oh. I'm. um...
God. there's like 50
people in our apartment.
statistically speaking.
and he's least two of them are sociopaths.
which is kind of cool.
Nice flowers.
Oh. they're. uh...
Housewarming gift.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh. okay.
Most people just brought beer and chips.
That's very nice.
Uh. I'm MJ.
I'm. uh...
Maynard.
Oh.
You two don't know each other?
No. I'm a neighbour.
Friendly neighbour?
I'm sorry.
So. how was the interview?
I'm gonna put these in water.
It was nice to meet you. Maynard.
Nerd.
Maynard.
Yeah.
Did you go?
Please tell me that you went.
Yes.
Ah!
And I got the job.
Oh. my God. MJ. That's amazing.
I turned it down.
What?
I don't want to work for
some soulless corporation.
The. they. not all soulless.
So. yes.
Okay. they're all mostly soulless.
but don't you want like. health insurance?
Yeah. of course I do. but at what cost?
Depends on your deductible.
Oh. you mean. like the principles?
Yes.
Sorry.
I don't know.
I know it sounds cheesy. but...
Something's just telling me that I'm supposed
to be waiting for something great. you know?
Okay. um. to. uh...
- Wait for something great.
- To waiting for something great.
Well. the wait is over.
Oh!
No!
Dude. this is top shelf!
Just like you.
Oh!
I'm gonna hide this.
I lifted this off him again.
But what if Ned needs the
fire of a thousand sharks?
You mean heart palpitation.
You can't save everyone.
I can try.
That's my girl.
Sorry.
When we get to MIT.
we should all live together!
- Yeah. for sure.
- Yeah. I'd love that.
We'll be a freshman.
We'll all be together.
Yeah. we'll be together. for sure.
You're gonna forget who I am.
We can't remember.
what're you talking about?
It's okay.
I'm gonna come and find you.
And I'll explain everything.
I love..
Wait and tell me when you see me again.
My name is Peter Parker.
And I...
would like a coffee.
Is there anything else?
No.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen
to me now that you've got powers?
You know. this whole
thing. can get really scary.
You know that?
Yeah. it's already pretty scary.
Yeah.
And things can change very quickly.
In ways that we can't
even imagine right now.
Believe me. I know.
I don't think you do know.
What do you mean?
Oh. I. uh...
I live here. I just don't...
I'm gonna grab my stuff.
Is that my shirt?
No.
Oh. how cute.
Come on.
Hi. Peter.
You have 107 new alerts.
Please check back log.
What?
What is happening?
The results of your body scan show a surge in
the hormones associated with your arachnid DNA.
Resulting in the formation of organic web spinerettes
nd dangerously heightened sensory receptors.
Okay. but I feel fine.
For long isolation or emotional trauma
could be contributing to this sudden change.
Have you experienced
any recent traumatic events?
Peter?
I'm fine. E.V..
You don't seem fine.
I recommend you take
some time to rebalance.
It's not really an option. is it?
Mechanical web shooters and organic
webs cannot be used simultaneously.
Come on. Peter.
Alert: Senses are overloaded.
Senses are overloaded.
Oh. what the hell was that?
Your heightened senses are taking
in too much information at once.
Okay. it's okay.
It's okay.
All right. organic webs.
Peter two had them.
He was cool.
Oh my god. that's hideous.
Okay. here we go.
Okay. that didn't work.
Organic webs.
Come on. and web.
What's going on. E.V.?
Shots fired at the Damage
Control data center in Manhattan.
Suspect facial match with Scorpion.
Okay. I'm on my way.
I don't know what you're looking for.
I'm looking for V-Max.
I don't know anything.
I'll see for myself.
I'm sorry. I'm late.
I've had a really crazy day.
Oh. Scorpion. do we really gotta
keep doing this? My head is killing me.
You think I'm Scorpion?
What?
What's happening to you?
Oh. you can't sense me anymore.
What's going on with you. Spider-Man?
Warning. Arachnid hormone is increasing.
Who are you?
Do you know who you are?
- We need some help over here.
- Yes. coming through.
Spider-Man.
What the hell?
Somebody get a medic.
DeWolff. was she hurt?
Is she okay?
No
Just let me go...
What is going on with you?
It wasn't Scorpion. okay?
I mean. it was...
But he was possessed. okay?
By whatever hijacked that tank.
Look. please. can I just...
- No!
- Alright. listen. slow down.
Listen. I don't know what this is.
I need you to pull it together.
You almost killed a cop.
This isn't you.
I know. I'm sorry
If you act like this. I cannot protect you.
Whatever this is. you need to fix it.
Through later us coma dynamics (?)
We can arrange time and space in a grid
Which allows us to simulate
the quartz binding into the protons.
Cindy. is this the question about
protons or more stuff about Avengers?
Okay
Guys. I love to tell stories
But you know. I got to teach
you some Physics at some point
All right. let it rip. Cindy
If Thanos was so worried
about overpopulation..
Why didn't you just use the
magic glove to make more food?
Arthur. you want to answer that question?
Hulk!
Smash!
There you have it.
Excuse me. Dr. Banner..
I am..
You okay?
Yeah. sorry. it's just a headache.
Have you got a minute?
I wanted to talk to you
about you about your inhibitor.
Oh. sure
Don't worry. it's got failsafe
I'm not going to turn into the big
green-raging monster machine in the cafeteria
But if you do see me with this thing off..
Run.
Raah!
No. but you're using target-specific
short-interfering RNA. right?
It's like gene silencing
You're just incorporating
the gamma radiation
What'd you say your name was?
Uh. Ned
Leeds
So you found a way to
suppress the expression of DNA
Even as it's undergoing the mutation
due to the gamma radiation. right?
Yes.
Okay. so my question is.
would that same thing be possible
with DNA that's mutating
for another reason?
What's the reason?
I don't know.
Let's say that the host you
know is mixed with some kind of..
Foreign DNA?
Theoretically.
Theoretically? Yes it's possible.
Yes.
So. could you suppress only
some parts of that DNA expression
like the bad aspects. but
just keep all the good stuff?
You mean. like if I wanted to
keep some parts of Hulk. but not all?
Right.
It would be enormously
dangerous and complex. but..
But if you were able to target
the correct mRNA strand..
Possibly.
Wait. so you could just turn
the mutating gene on and off..
As long as you do it before
the mRNA transcription?
Maybe.
I mean. if you apply the same
thinking. you could even develop
some kind of automatic
inhibitor that would just adjust
to any type of mutation.
Well. now you're talking about a
universal inhibitor that would control..
Anyone who has any powers.
It's a dangerous idea.
Well. yeah. but it's theoretical. right?
You're not one of my students. are you?
No. I'm a grad student.
I've. uh. taken enough of your time.
I gotta get some books back to the library.
The library is that way.
Right.
I'll go.
How would you decide?
What's that?
Well. what parts of
nature were good or bad?
What if you're trying to control
the expression of something..
That needs to be expressed?
Good luck with your studies. Ned.
Thank you. Professor.
Like reptiles. animals. and caterpillars.
Spiders sheds skin at key
points of their life cycles.
The process known as molting.
Fourth inhibitor prototype complete.
Okay.
It can leave the spider vulnerable..
Upload inhibitor. beta build.. Seven.
Uploaded.
Would you like to run a test?
Yeah. run it.
Spiders have three
stages in their life cycle.
Each stage is characterized
by physical changes.
With the largest changes occurring
during the beautiful transition
to adulthood.
For those will make it through..
Molting amounts to a kind of rebith.
Can you turn that spider stuff off?
Turning off video.
Inhibitor active.
Come on. come on.
Keep an eye on my vitals.
Inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing arachnid
hormones to your baseline levels.
Okay.
All right. E.V..
Let's do this.
Initiating field test 1.
That's working.
Alert.
Inhibitor is overheating.
Functionality reducing.
Yeah.
I'm sensing that.
Alert.
Senses are overloaded.
Web grenades activated.
Inhibitor field test 1: Failure.
Yo. Spider-Man.
You okay?
Yeah.
I'm just trying out some new tech.
Oh. yeah?
To get rid of that monster inside you.
Still can't sense me. huh?
Guess your technology isn't working.
You know. you're the only
person I've met that I can't hop into.
I'm sure that's really frustrating for you.
Well. I'll get in there one day.
What do you want?
I don't know why I half-human. half-spider
would decide to work for an organization..
Whose sworn mission is to hunt
down anybody who's different?
Damage Control is an
afternoon because you're different.
They're hunting you down
because you're dangerous.
Now. what do you want?
Since you're a very simple spider.
Let me spell it out for you.
Damage Control has something that I need.
Oh. you mean V-Max?
I was planning to use Scorpion to get it.
But you keep getting in my way.
I will always be in your way.
You sure about that. Peter Parker?
You know. your apartment
is kind of like a parody..
Where you think a sad
single guy in his 20s might live.
Take out containers.
Free weights.
Protein powder.
You're bluffing.
You know you're not
hard to track down. Peter?
Well. at least..
Not for someone like me.
I did find one interesting thing. though.
In the wrong places..
Coffee cup.
E.V.. display homework station.
You spent four years of erasing
Peter Parker from existence?
No wonder the spider's
trying to swallow up the man.
I wonder if MJ would even recognise you.
Oh. God.
I think I might go see how she's doing.
I'm not going to let that happen.
No.
Her roommate was nice enough
to post a new address online.
How about this?
I'll race you.
If you touch her..
Better start swinging..
I'm fast.
Hey.
It's a long way to MJ's.
You better pick up the pace.
E.V.. track physical anomalies.
Searching for physical
anomalies between subjects.
Please stand by.
Thank you all so much for coming today.
I'm sorry about that.
Give it up for Spider-Man.
It race for the love of his
life. and it's not looking good.
Come on. Spidey. Keep up.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
E.V.. run these numbers with the others.
Analysing jump distances from patterns.
Get in the jump data.
Calculating.
Come on. I need an answer.
Calculations complete.
You have a limit to your
job radius. don't you?
33 feet.
I don't see anybody up
here for you to hop into.
Very clever.
Like I said. you're not getting near her.
I'm sorry but you're in danger.
Where's your roommate?
- What?
- Where is Ned?
In Boss with friends. Why?
You've got to come with me.
I don't know if you're the real Spider-Man.
I'm not coming with you.
We don't have time for
this. Please come on.
You need to get out of my apartment.
This is going to sound insane but there is someone
who is after you who is really dangerous. okay?
I promised you that I would keep you safe.
Please. you just have to trust me. Come on.
Fine.
Web. Stop.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. yeah. I'm fine.
Okay. we should be safe up here.
Okay. safe from what?
Uh. I'm not entirely sure.
Okay. well. what do they want with me?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why would they choose me?
Well. I wish I could tell you.
We knew each other. didn't we?
What?
It's the only explanation.
It's been driving me crazy for years all the
times that Spider-Man saved either me or Ned.
It was the Washington Monument and then it
was London and Prague and the Night Monkey.
I mean. twice is a coincidence
but over and over again..
We knew each other. Tell me I'm wrong.
Well. you're wrong.
Well. were we were we classmates
or our friends or something?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Were we something more?
I just. I can't remember and I feel
like someone scrambled my brain..
And you're the only one who would know why.
This is crazy.
I know that you can't tell me the truth.
But I need to know.
Maybe there's a part of
me that still remembers.
- Peter.
- MJ
I've missed you so much.
I can't believe you figured it out.
I did.
Go ahead. Peter.
Touch her.
Hold her.
You've been wanting to do this for so long.
True Love Kiss breaks his spell
and reunites to star-crossed lovers.
MJ would vomit.
You really are a simple spider. aren't you?
I see why you like her.
She's a...
She's smart.
Funny.
And a little dark and twisted.
I mean. it is sad.
There is like no thoughts of you in here.
Once or ever.
But you knew that didn't you?
You're a monster.
If you loved someone
the way that I loved her.
you'd know that what you're
doing right now is unforgivable.
Oh. is that so?
You know. some people would kill to
hold the person they love one last time.
Stop it. now.
You're running out of time. Peter.
Soon enough. it won't just be your friends
who don't remember you're Peter Parker.
Maybe you should
write a letter to yourself.
Get out of her.
Who's the monster now. Peter?
What?
MJ. No. no. no. Oh God.
Oh God. please.
Now. come on.
Come on. come on. come on.
Oh. thank God. thank God.
Oh. you're okay.
Well. you're okay.
Oh. I'm so sorry.
Stop.
Well. please stop.
Please. don't quit.
You win. you win. you win.
You win. you win.
Just don't hurt her.
You're a mess. Spider-Man.
Anytime I want.
I can be anyone I want.
So you can't protect MJ..
Even from yourself.
It really is a nice letter.
Little heavy-handed.
But not bad.
You're okay.
I'm going to take you someplace safe.
Come on.
Take me to 3165 Live Island Street.
Navigating to the Empire State University.
I got you. I got you.
- Are you sure?
- Yup
- Cause I feel like I'm slipping a little bit.
- You're not slipping. - Okay
- You're okay.
- I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine.
- Can we just slow down for like two seconds?
- Well. we're almost there.
Yeah. yeah. but you just
told me I was mind controlled.
Well. not technically.
I mean. you're lucky I
believe in that stuff. okay?
Because governments have been
doing it for years. especially the French.
Are you okay?
Yeah. look. sorry.
I'm just trying to take you
someplace safe. okay?
I don't feel safe.
Ah.
You're losing it. kid.
I thought you'd be able to
see that coming a mile away.
What is wrong with you?
You could've killed us.
Excuse me?
You show up to my house unannounced.
what you think is gonna happen?
Wait. this is your house?
Who the hell is that?
Who the hell are you?
She's um...
You know?
No. I don't know.
It's why I just asked you.
She's in danger. Frank.
Look. I need your help. okay?
Yeah. it looks like it.
Well. come on. you owe me.
Ah. come on.
Aren't you sick of this story?
Staten Island.
Nah. that's not an island.
What more do you want me to do?
I literally saved your life.
You're out of your mind. kid!
- What. I gotta save it twice to get a favour out of you?
- That guy could've hit you with a handful of rice.
I mean. what does that sound like to you?
- I had him where I want him. I'm seeing him right there.
- A drug dealer was gonna shoot a guy. then I webbed the gun.
Okay. fine. go ahead.
What does that sound like to you?
I don't care.
I just want to go home.
That's an excellent idea.
Kick rocks. go away.
No. wait. wait. wait.
wait. wait. Frank. wait.
Please.
Hey. I've got to keep her safe. okay?
And I don't have anywhere else to go.
You like chili?
I made chili.
All right. just...
Watch out for the claymores.
Don't want to pick up pieces
of you for the next two weeks.
Hey. I definitely would not eat that chili.
So you're telling me that maniac
that was behind all that tech nonsense
is nothing but a goddamn teenager?
And it's not just the tank.
It's every attack on Damage
Control this past month.
How does a kid learn how to drive a tank?
I don't know. Frank.
Beat you all over the street like that.
She did not beat me.
Is this your family?
Would you get the hell away from that?
Look. I got one rule in this house.
You don't touch anything.
You don't move anything.
You sure as shit don't has many
goddamn questions about anything.
So three rules.
Is see why you like her.
You can go put some pants on.
Don't touch the chili.
I like him.
What was she doing?
So I managed to pull
those image from my fight
and then run them through system.
Who is she?
Until a couple of months ago?
Nobody.
She was in and out of foster care.
psych hospitals.
and then eventually she ran
away and dropped off the grid.
There's hardly any information about her.
There hasn't been scrubbed.
but she's classified as a telepath.
And now we have a name.
Jean Gray.
Yeah.
These are the Damage Control
sites that she hasn't hit yet.
So if she surfaces.
then my facial tracking
program will pick her up.
Right.
Oh yeah? What then?
Well. don't worry about "what then."
Just look after her.
Don't worry about it. huh?
I'm just supposed to sit here
and babysit your girlfriend?
I don't need to be babysat. so yeah
She's not my girlfriend.
All right. all right.
Look. what's the plan. huh?
Just gotta hope that your
facial tracking program works?
And you get yourself killed.
I gotta watch her the rest of my life?
I'm not going to get killed. Frank.
I can catch her. okay?
I just have to fix my inhibitor
and then I'll be good to go.
Well. what do you need to do that?
Frank.
You do not have what
I need to do that. okay?
You know you've got some mouth on you.
What do you think you
have an anti-static mat...?
A tonal probe and a micro tools?
I got all that shit.
What for?
Bombs.
Bingo.
Unbelievable.
Hey. do you think it's safe
to maybe call someone
and let them know I'm okay?
Like your boyfriend?
No.
Like my roommate.
Oh.
I don't think that's such
a good idea. you know?
Because she already knows who he is
and she can inhabit anyone she wants.
All right. Yeah.
Yeah.
You're right.
Sorry.
No. it's fine.
I totally get it.
If I called my boyfriend..
He'd just ask me a bunch of
questions that I couldn't answer..
And he'd tell me I was
being withholding again.
Withholding?
Yep.
Sounds like your
boyfriend's kind of a jerk.
But why would he think you're withholding?
I don't know. You tell me.
masked vigilante behind the curtain.
Um.
Okay.
I see your point.
So what about you?
What about me?
Well. do you have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Do I have Mrs. Spider-Man?
Um.
No.
Why not?
Why not? Because. um..
I'm too withholding. obviously.
Welcome to the club.
Yeah.
There was someone.
Huh?
Yeah. yeah. yeah.
What happened?
I. uh..
I had to let her go.
To keep her safe.
I'm sorry. I must have
been really hard for you.
Yeah. it was. yeah.
It is.
It is really hard.
Oh!
Are you okay?
Yeah. yeah. yeah. I'm okay.
I. uh..
You know what. I'm gonna come over.
Hold on. hold on. hold on.
hold on. hold on. hold on.
What's going on?
Um.
It just keeps overheating on me.
It's been stumping me for days.
Before I switched to aerospace.
I was going to major in
biochemical engineering. so..
Do you mind if I...?
Oh. yeah.
Sure. here.
There you go.
Wow.
So. does the device itself. I mean.
does it generate any kind of radiation
or a magnetic field?
Because I would definitely interfere.
Oh. yeah. it has a micro magnetic field.
but I accounted for that in the design.
Okay. well. what about your suit?
Oh. it actually dissipates into the fabric.
which is pretty cool.
Okay.
What about those?
What about what?
Your goggles. or whatever you call them.
Uh. they would create a field.
It would be tiny. but..
But it's on your head.
which is very close to the inhibitor.
Which is probably why it's overheating.
Oh. MJ. that is genius.
Okay. this has to work.
An inhibitor engaged.
Suppressing selected arachnid hormones.
Okay. that feels better.
That feels totally better.
Oh. my head feels so clear.
And I'm not shooting organic webs.
Oh. my God. MJ. that like. totally worked.
You know. this is some really intense stuff
you're working on here.
Well. yeah. it's really important.
Yeah. but this is like.
I mean. this is like altering your DNA.
I mean. this is the
kind of stuff you put on.
like. I don't know. like a monster.
Well. if you've seen what's been happening
to me over the last couple of days.
then you might understand.
Yeah. well. I've been with
you for the last few hours..
And that's not what I've seen.
And what have you seen?
From my side of the curtain?
A really good guy. that
might just be changing.
I don't mean to overstep.
I'll let you get back into it.
Can't sleep either. huh?
You want coffee?
Sure.
You get your shit fixed?
Yeah. I've been wearing it all night.
So far. so good.
I made this other one universal.
So if I could get it on Jean.
it should completely shut down her powers.
You know what else would work?
You just shoot her.
Nice.
That's got to be the goofiest
shit I've ever seen in my life.
What. you can't even take the mask off
to drink a cup of coffee?
Don't take it personally. Frank.
It stays on for everybody.
Even her?
Who is she. kid?
I don't know.
That's horseshit. Who is she?
I'm telling you. I don't know who she is.
- You're pretending not to. Why?
- I don't care about her.
I don't know who she is. Frank.
I don't have anybody.
I'm like you.
I just keep to myself.
You're like me?
What do you know about me. kid?
You think this is a choice?
Living like this. it's a lifestyle?
Is that what you think?
Kid. this is a sentence.
You know somethin'..
If I had one second..
People I love were still breathing.
you think I'd hide behind a mask?
You think I'd pretend to
be something that I'm not?
Acting like a goddamn coward?
I got a facial match.
She's at the Damage
Control HQ in Manhattan.
I gotta go. okay?
She's gonna be okay.
I'll see to it.
Thanks. Frank.
Hey.
You're just gonna let him go by himself?
You know. I think he might need you.
Eh...
Kind of like you need him on Staten Island.
You can't hide from me forever. Bill.
You've got a strong door.
but it's the world you have to worry about.
Who are you and what do you want?
I'm Jean Gray.
You know what I want.
Jean?
You look me up?
I'm blushing.
I told you what would happen
to your girl if you got in my way.
You're not getting near her again.
Adn you're definitely not
getting inside that vault.
Maybe not.
But this guy might.
Jean. you don't know
what you're dealing with.
You know. you and Banner
have a lot in common.
Both fighting with losing battle
against the monster that lives inside you.
Jean. this is the Hulk. you can't just...
Aw!
What the hell?
Oh. I see.
Trying to muzzle me
like you muzzle yourself?
I can't let you in there.
Whatever V-Max is. you're not getting it.
Like hell I'm not.
Oh. crap!
No.
Jean. don't do this.
Save your breath.
Frank. what are you doing here?
What do you think I'm doing?
Saving your..
This is way above your pay grade. dude!
- We're fighting the Hulk!
- Oh shit!
Really?
Get out!
- Stop shooting him!
- Are you out of your goddamn mind?
Banner's not the problem. She is.
I thought I told you to
stay home and watch MJ.
Yeah. you did.
And then she tells me I
gotta come watch you.
Wait. did she actually say that to you?
Are you blushing. daffodil?
I'm not blushing.
Goddamn it. I knew I
should've brought a bigger gun.
That's a good idea. "bring a bigger gun".
What are you gonna do?
Tickle him in the death?
No. look. change of plan.
First we get this on the
Hulk. then we go after Jean.
I got one better.
That's the highest
casualty producing threat.
You contain it. I go find the source.
I take it down. You got it?
Are you just trying to get
out of fighting the Hulk?
- I guess so.
- OK. whatever. dude.
- Wait. no. Frank. Frank. Frank.
- What?
Do not kill her!
Don't start with that soft serve bullshit.
You know something? I'm gonna do this.
I'm gonna do it my way.
Just go.
Don't give her the 33 feet.
So frustrating!
Hey.
Whoa.
This guy's got issues.
Oh no.
No. no. again.
Dr. Banner?
Is that you?
Spider-Man.
What happened?
Hey. hey. hey.
Did I do that?
Yeah.
Did I hurt anyone?
It's not your fault.
She was in your mind.
You weren't in control.
I lost my inhibitor.
Look here. here.
It's the only thing
keeping the monster inside.
It's okay.
I got another one.
I just need you to put this on.
What is it?
It's universal.
It should work on you.
Please. sir. there's people
in the building. Just put it on.
Oh.
You okay?
My head. I think she broke something.
Is she still in there?
No.
It's the other guy.
Bruce?
Look. I could get you out of here. okay?
I just need you to put that inhibitor on.
Get away from me!
It's happening.
I can't control..
Yes. you can. Bruce.
Yes. you can.
Get out of the building!
No!
Get everyone out of the..
Banner. please. look at me.
No Banner. no girl. Only Hulk!
I didn't know you can get that big.
Whoa!
Good luck with that. Peter.
There you are!
Yes!
Just hold still!
No lethal rounds.
Tracking time to detonation.
97 seconds to detonation.
I know! I know!
Why's your skin so thick?
Inihibor cannot attach.
Dr. Banner!
Please!
Bruce!
It's Peter!
I'm your friend.
Bruce!
Throw down your guns. or
you'll get the next one in the head.
Where is she?
What?
It's over. Jean.
Sara.
Is that my gun?
Is anyone hurt. or it's just me?
Is anyone hurt?
Spider-Man!
You saved my life.
Andn you saved God knows how many lives.
by making sure she didn't find
what she was looking for in there.
Before she passed out.
she tried to say something.
A name: Sara.
Does that mean something to you?
Before you got the inhibitor on her.
she managed to get to my mind for a moment.
Sara was the name of someone I
worked closely with that recently passed.
I'm sorry to hear that.
Somehow the memory of
Sara must have affected her.
Well. I'd love to talk to her when
she wakes up. if that's all right.
Of course. she'll be transferred
to our facility in Roosevelt Island.
I'm just as eager to get
her talking as you are.
but let's not strain her
too much in one day.
Yeah. of course.
Thank you. Spider-Man.
My pleasure.
Okay.
MJ. it worked. She's in custody.
You're safe now.
You left this?
Did you want me to find it?
No.
No. no.
Look. I can explain. okay?
Can you take that off. please?
What?
The mask.
I think I deserve to have this
conversation with "Peter Parker".
You came to the party at
our apartment the other night.
And the donut shop.
The year I went off to school.
Why didn't you tell me then?
I was trying to protect you.
I've almost been killed like.
five times the past 24 hours..
So it's not really working that well.
I know. I'm sorry. I..
Were you ever going to tell me?
Right.
So you're just going to
make that decision for me?
I know. I'm sorry.
I don't really need you to
keep saying that you're sorry.
I don't know what you want me to tell you.
I want you to tell me why
you would do this to me.
I lost someone.
And they'd still be
here if it wasn't for me.
I didn't read you that letter because..
I didn't want anything
like that to happen to you.
That's not really your decision.
I know it's not. but..
You mean everything to me.
And I've been trying to
live my life without you. but..
I can't.
I love you.
This spell or whatever it is that you did..
It worked.
All these memories that you're
saying that we have together.
I don't..
I don't have them.
And I do see why. you know.
and she would love. the girl you..
Wrote that letter to. but..
I understand..
That you did what you
had to do to protect her.
And for that. I'm so grateful.
But I..
I don't love you.
You said I don't. I don't even know you.
I should probably go now.
I really am sorry. Peter.
I don't have a phone. Do
you mind taking me home?
Yeah. of course.
Thank you.
Yeah. sure.
I'm gonna...
Oh. yeah. Yeah. of course.
Do you want to come up?
Just to say hi to Ned. maybe?
I would love that.
The Hulk. aka Dr. Bruce Banner. is in custody.
currently being transferred to a psychiatric ward.
Oh. so sad.
After years as a peaceful academic. the question
the world asked today is. "what happened?"
Hey. I'm nearby.
And then?
Yeah.
Hey. I'm nearby.
Huh.
You're not gonna believe this.
But the Spidey-tracker app says
that Spider-Man is in the direct vicinity.
Oh. yeah?
No way. that's crazy.
Uh. Ned?
Spider-Man?
Spider-Man. Ned?
It's nice to meet you. Ned.
Hello.
I'm not like a weirdo for anything.
He's a little weird.
Why?
Why are you here?
Oh. I...
I was on the subway.
Platform. right.
And she's on her phone.
Yeah. I double distracted
and the train was coming.
And I just swooped her right up.
Yeah. saved the day.
Oh. my God.
Why has that never happened to me?
So. what if you're a mid-swing
and you decide you need a pee?
Do you just land on top of a building?
What?
Do you drop down the ground
level and run into a coffee shop?
You're like. hey. Spider-Man. I need a pee.
Or do you find a rooftop somewhere?
No. I don't find a rooftop somewhere. Ned.
Is this really what you want
to be asking him right now?
Yeah. dude. come on.
You can ask me anything.
You want to know how my web shoiters work?
I mean. I already know
how the web shooters work.
Is that right?
Well. there's obviously some
sort of sheer thinning fluid
that is cycling within a chamber. right?
So you can keep this liquid form.
And then when you activate
it by pressing on the triggers.
it runs through a Teflon turbine.
And then it hardens when
it interacts with the air.
Right?
I mean. not exactly. but...
Okay. okay.
Well. then tell me what's in the web fluid.
I would guess something
like a long chain polymer.
A nylon?
That's pretty close.
Okay. okay.
What about Romax or...
Or. Kevlar!
"All right then. keep your secrets."
"If you are referring to the
indicident with the dragon..
I was very much involved."
"All I did was simply give your uncle
a little nudge out the door."
Solid reference.
Ooh. Banh Mi time.
You ordered Banh Mi's?
I ordered five Banh Mi's.
We have Spider-Man in the apartment.
He's going to get fed.
Sorry about him.
He's just like very
excited that you're here.
Are you kidding?
It's like the most fun I've had in years.
I really miss you guys.
You guys really do look like best friends.
What do you mean?
You should tell him.
He can handle it.
Yeah. I know.
Um...
When she was inhabiting you.
on the rooftop.
she kissed me..
And I kissed her back..
Because I thought it was you.
but I didn't know.
And I'm really sorry.
I just thought you should know.
Thanks for telling me.
I mean. it's not like.
I remember anything anyway. so...
Really?
Yeah.
It was weird.
It was like one second I
was sitting in my desk..
And the next second I
was lying on the street.
I don't know. like. a
light switch went off.
What?
So you don't remember anything?
No. why?
Metzger said. he remembered
thinking about someone named Sara.
but what you're saying is that
you don't remember anything at all.
I mean. yeah. it was instantaneous.
That's what made it so scary.
He lied to me.
I heard you call a leshy.
Yeah. her name's Jean Grey.
I need some help determining
the size of some potatoes.
- Potatoes?
- I think that's Black Widow.
I think Metzger lied to me about a name.
Can you see if there's a
connection between Jean
and someone named Sara?
Hmm.
This potato sound meager.
Oh. well. that really is your office.
Well. well. well.
Internet. government records.
and a lot of data related to Jean Grey
has been scrubbed by Damage Control.
They know about what?
Her sister.
Wait. Jean has a sister?
Yeah. Sara Grey.
Also with telepath.
Damage Control took her into custody
for study and observation.
Wow.
You probably can guess
what they meant by that.
Experimentation and other
human rights violations.
Yes. exactly.
Wait. who are you?
Hi.
Ned Leeds. Big fan.
Oh. I'm sorry.
I'm just so happy that
this person has friends.
Thanks.
I owe you one.
Good luck. Spider-Man.
Bye.
She was just looking for her sister.
and I handed it to the people who took her.
I gotta go.
Peter.
Just be careful. all right?
Oh. well.
Spider-Man's name is Peter.
Jean. who do you want to be?
Her. in the jacket.
She's too far.
You're gonna have to hop.
Hop?
First. pick something close.
And then...
The hop has a limit.
But you can string them
together and go as far as you want.
And when you let go...
You're back where you started.
Can you do that to
everyone in this park at once?
Well. yeah. maybe one day.
If you get really good.
No.
Now could she just send us away?
She wasn't really a mom.
Not like that. anyway.
She was.
Before we changed.
And if that's all it takes for
you to stop being a mom.
then you're not a mom.
What would you do if
you had daughters like us?
I'd love them.
Especially the redhead one.
Shut up.
We have each other.
And give me an ice cream.
One mint chip. one chocolate?
Sara?!
I'm sorry. Jean.
I have to keep you safe.
Subject is awake. heart rate is 94 BPM.
Jean. that's not going to work anymore.
Thanks to Spider-Man.
Jean...
I need you to breathe.
I need you to look at me and breathe.
You're safe. Breathe.
Where is she?
Like your sister. you've been blessed with a power that
has the potential to do tremendous good in the world..
Or tremendous damage.
The power like yours in the hands
of a child is an impossible burden.
But imagine...
If that power was placed in the hands of
people who actually know what to do with it.
Where is my sister?
You're going to change the world. Jean.
Hey!
No!
I know where you are
and what are you doing.
Oh. yeah. how's that?
I Got eyes everywhere. kid.
Look. Frank.
Damage Control kidnapped Gene's sister.
Jean was just trying to find her.
We were wrong about everything.
Sentimental horseshit.
You've seen what she can do. what she's
capable of. what you're gonna let her loose?
Is that what you're going to do?
Tell you right now you do that.
I'll handle it my way.
Frank. listen to me. You just..
Frank!
Distance check?
Forty-foot clearance.
Locking down the room.
Disengage inhibitor.
Jean. your powers are
now fully operational.
As you can tell. you're
beyond your jump radius.
Tell me what V-Max is.
You're the second person
to ask me about that.
I have no idea what that means.
She sent me a message.
She was trying to help me find her.
She communicated with you
telepathically across all that distance?
We did register a huge
spike in that session.
Fascinating.
What does it mean?
I don't know.
Let's begin.
Our work with Sara is central on two areas.
Identifying the source of her power and
identifying her path towards copying you.
If we could find a way to record
a telepathic brain during a jump.
then perhaps we could replicate those
pathways in the mind of our choosing.
This instrument is your sister's legacy.
We built this together
over many months of trial.
I hope you and I can honor her sacrifice.
What are you talking about?
Trigger the first jump.
Tell me what V-max is.
I know that's where you're hiding her.
She's jumping.
Copy.
We're in full lockdown.
The process has commenced.
What process?
Hey. whoa. that's a pretty
serious look there. dude.
Hey. whoa. what the hell. man?
Come on. I'm a friend of Damage Control.
What are you doing?
Huh.
It's going to be like that. You want to go.
All right. All right. just give me a sec.
Give me a sec.
I'm not in high school anymore.
Oh... Do you stretch?
Are you a big stretcher?
You should do it in your line of work.
What about you? You guys stretch?
It's so good for you.
You ready?
Watch your head!
Where is Jean Gray?
It's jump 26.
Recording looks good.
Excuse me. sir.
We have an intruder.
Oh.
You're right.
She's much stronger than her sister.
Increase the frequency.
You're doing very well. Jean.
Jean.
Jean. can you hear me?
Jean?
You're a murderer.
Her frequencies are evolving.
This doesn't make sense.
The last thing my sister saw was this room.
A brainwaves is somehow
affecting the objects around her.
- Shut it down.
- I'm trying. sir.
What do you mean you're trying?
The last thing my sister
saw was this God damn room!
- Shut it down!
- I can't. sir.
I can't let you do that. Bill.
The only hand that wields
this power.. Are mine.
What do you want?
Jean. I'm here to help you.
You put me here.
I know. and I'm sorry about Sara.
and I'm sorry that I got it so wrong.
If you came here to save the helpless
girl from Damage Control. you're too late.
They're the ones who need saving.
And now. so do you.
Here we go.
God. that's cool.
I'm here to help you.
Jean. Jean. please!
Come on. come on. come on!
What?
Isn't it funny how your friends from Damage
Control developed a special weapon just for you?
They've got a whole task force ready.
Just in case you ever get out of line.
People are monsters.
You shouldn't trust them
any more than they trust you.
I'm a little busy. Frank!
We got a problem. kid.
She got a hold of everyone
within a kilometer of the island.
Wait. what?
Look. if you're going to do
something. you gotta do it now.
I'm trying!!
Kid! Shit!
My sister died in this room.
Surrounded by these men.
And her only crime
was that she was special.
Just like you.
Just like me.
People like us don't
get to live a normal life.
We don't get to have friends or family.
Those people are gone.
That life is over.
So why don't you just
be honest with yourself?
Are you Peter Parker?
Or are you Spider-Man?
I'm both.
Jane. please.
This will make you right.
Come on. you're not a killer. Jean.
You have no idea what I am.
I know that you loved your sister.
And I know that losing her
felt like you'd lost everything.
If you come any closer.
he dies! They all do!
You know this won't
bring her back. right. Jean?
Don't be so sure I
can't get into your mind.
I'm a lot more powerful since I last tried.
Go ahead.
Hey.
You think you don't have to listen
to me. now you've got powers?
You know. this whole
thing. can get really scary.
You know that?
It's already pretty scary.
And things can change very quickly.
In ways that we can't
even imagine right now.
I know.
I don't think you do now.
What do you mean?
You're a really special person.
And I would hope that that will always
make you feel really great about yourself.
But I know sometimes it doesn't.
Sometimes it'll be really lonely.
And sometimes. because you're special.
people can do dark.
monstrous things to you.
But this is what I want you to know.
You're beautiful..
And the people who love you. we love you..
Not because you're special.
we love you. because you're you.
I want you to remember that.
Even when you feel
like you're totally alone.
That's your deepest responsibility.
Never forget that. no matter
how powerful you become.
Hey.
I'm sorry about your. sister.
I'm sorry about your aunt.
Yeah. you would've loved her.
Just because we've lost someone..
It doesn't mean we have to do this alone.
I mean. we can't. Trust
me. I've been trying.
It doesn't work.
Even if that's true.
I have no one.
You have me.
No.
You hurt?
No. I'm fine.
- Peter.
- I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
Peter. No. no. no.
No. no. no. no. Peter.
You gotta get out of here.
No. please just stay with me.
Come on. hold on. come on. Please!
You're gonna be okay.
Just go.
Yeah. look at me.
Shock today.
As spider man arrived to Bellevue
Hospital with a bullet wound..
Seemingly at that death's door.
The reclusive crime fighter is in critical condition
as the city's top medical experts work to save him.
Tonight. all eyes are on Spider-Man.
The hero who saved New York so many times is
now in the hands of its best and brightest.
And the people of New
York hold their breath.
Frank.
Where am I?
- No. no. no. no. no. Wear your mask.
- Where's my mask?
Don't worry. I've got you covered.
You're good.
Where's Jean? Is she okay?
- Yeah. she's okay.
- Where is she?
I think she just left.
She was using her magic
voodoo shit to keep you alive.
Yeah. she's all right.
I'm sorry.
- No. Frank. it's okay.
- I'm sorry for what I did.
I know it's a lot of things. but it
sure as shit wasn't okay. all right?
I've seen..
I've seen real bravery. kid. in my day.
But that... that was something else.
- You crying. Frank?
- No. I ain't crying!
No. you're looking the exactly
the way I thought you would.
A nice kid.
I've never had a friend like that.
Are we friends now?
I can't believe I just saw you cry.
I didn't cry. What are you talking about?
Oh. yeah.
They've been doing it all night.
they've been here since you walked in.
Just take a look.
Yo. kid.
When you came in they had to cut through the suit.
but when you're ready to split. I got a plan.
Hey. it's Spider-Man!
I've. uh...
Been thinking a lot about what you said.
And you'd be happy to
know that I've decided I'm not..
I'm not going to do this alone anymore.
I miss you. May.
I mean. I still got a little pain in my back. but I could
probably get back out there if you need me for anything.
What I need you to do is rest.
I know. I know.
Well. come on. you gotta give me something.
I mean. how's the investigation going?
Well. that's good.
Don't you see?
But your friend. Black Widow. she's been
helping us get through all the records.
Damage Control tried to have scrubbed.
Had me dropped by her office the other day.
And how was that?
Well. my skin feels amazing.
Attention. all units.
We have a confirmed
bank robbery in progress.
Hey. are you getting this?
Yeah. I'm on it.
Hey. it's not that far from me.
I could probably meet you down there.
No. we can handle a robbery.
Just try to take care of yourself.
Okay.
You too.
Say hello to E.J. and Marley for me.
Okay.
Spider-Man says hello.
Hi.
Hey.
Oh. but flower guy. right? From the party?
- I'm Peter.
- Okay. hello.
Peter.